<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Glow</title>
        <item>
            <title>1.0.6</title>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 22:09:44 -0500</pubDate>
            <sparkle:version>272</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>1.0.6</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>26.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>Fullscreen & Multi-Monitor</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>Smarter Fullscreen Detection:</strong> Introduced an observer pattern for per-display fullscreen state tracking, ensuring accurate behavior across multiple monitors.</li>
                    <li><strong>Improved Compatibility:</strong> Expanded the list of ignored applications for fullscreen detection to include screen recording processes.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>Performance Optimizations</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>Faster Event Handling:</strong> Streamlined segment update handling and event monitoring with reactive debounce for improved responsiveness.</li>
                    <li><strong>Direct Frame Updates:</strong> Replaced NotificationCenter-based frame updates with direct callback handlers, reducing overhead and improving efficiency.</li>
                    <li><strong>Reduced Main Thread Contention:</strong> Offloaded heavy accessibility IPC operations to a dedicated background worker, minimizing UI freezes.</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>Cache & Accessibility Enhancements</h3>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>Animation-Aware Caching:</strong> Cache refreshes are now deferred during active animations, preventing unnecessary operations and improving smoothness.</li>
                    <li><strong>Smarter Retry Logic:</strong> User-initiated retries and settings access now bypass the circuit breaker for more reliable cache updates.</li>
                    <li><strong>Enhanced Global Monitor Activation:</strong> Improved logic for global monitor activation with added stability.</li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
            </description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/mrmango1/glow-releases/releases/download/1.0.6/Glow-1.0.6.dmg" length="7743816" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="vhwLy1s2WOQZbZLck8a0GBu3xbXyxln97REwFow+iHS4X8oaYjBLFWwCLOqcSDS2ld6mxevYO3kK4P5YWi+6DQ=="/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>